<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <description>
      A blog about spirituality, meditations, and rituals!
    </description>
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Supradivine Meditation</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/10/supradivine-meditation/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>Do 10 shallow breaths and then 15 deep ones. Then, do 20 deep breaths and 10 shallow ones. Repeat 2X more for a total of 3 times. Hold on to your supradivine philosopher stone! While holding, do 10 shallow breaths and hold for 20 seconds!</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>This makes you supradivine! Enjoy!</p>
</blockquote>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/10/supradivine-meditation/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Magick Meditation</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/10/magick-meditation/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>To start using magick with Alchemy!</p>

<p>Time: 1min.
Sound: Music, your pick</p>

<p>Do 4 deep breaths in any position you wish. Hold for 30 seconds.</p>

<p>That’s it! You’re set to use Magick with Alchemy! What will you make?</p>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/10/magick-meditation/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Higher Chakra Stones</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/10/higher-chakra-stones/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>8th: Sapphire</p>

<p>9th: Emerald</p>

<p>10th: Ruby</p>

<p>11th: Morganite</p>

<p>12th: Diamond</p>

<hr />

<p>Buddha Stone (nirvana): Selenite, specially charged!</p>

<p>Instructions on how to use it to commune with Buddhas in other notes <a href="/spiritual_energy//2022/11/10/buddas/">here!</a> Check it out! Have some tea with the Buddhas. (Non-divine beings).</p>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/10/higher-chakra-stones/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Accessing 20+ Chakras</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/10/chakras-20+/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>Time: 20min.</p>

<p>Sound: Lambda Waves</p>

<p>Stone: Shungite Philosopher Stone or Plain Shungite</p>

<p>Drink 4oz of quintessence before this meditation. Do 5 standing breaths before being seated! Now, while being seated, do 70 deep breaths! Hold for 50 seconds. Drink 4oz of quintessence and continue breathing deeply for 30 breaths and 30 shallow ones. End breathing with an 80 second hold.</p>

<p>This takes you from chakra 19 to 20, 21, 22, 23, …, to the last chakra! You’ve traveled them all! How’s it feel?! Power? Energy? Supra-divine? Going a notch past divine? The last chakra is a multiple of…8! So, it is for supra-divine beings!</p>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/10/chakras-20+/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Accessing 13-19 Chakras</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/10/chakras-13-19/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>Time: 15min.</p>

<p>Sound: Lambda Waves</p>

<p>Stone: Shungite Philosopher Stone or Plain Shungite</p>

<p>Drink 4oz of quintessence before meditation to charge the body. Start with 20 shallow breaths and then 40 deep breaths. Then, drink 4oz of quintessence again during the meditation. Now, hold the breath for 30sec. and continue with 30 deep breaths and 20 shallow ones! Hold the breath for 70 seconds!</p>

<p>You should have dipped from the 12th to the 13th and after this, you are traveling the rest until the 19th! Good work! This isn’t easy to do, not for most of us! How’s it feel? Chakra 19?</p>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/10/chakras-13-19/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Accessing Buddhas</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/10/buddas/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>So you want to be with the Buddhas? Okay, I’m about to tell you how to hang out with them and relax during meditation.</p>

<p>Drink nothing but tap water. No ice! Chilled is better. You can sweeten it with brown sugar if you want.</p>

<p>When you come back, drink some matcha, brown sugar if fine. Cold brew! No milk in matcha too. No ginger as well nor mint. Plain matcha optionally sweetened.</p>

<p>Hold on to the Buddha stone with your left hand; don’t let it see sunlight during this process!</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Do this after having the first meal or at 04:00-05:00. It works best during this time! Let the food digest for maybe 60-90min. before trying. You need to not be full.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Let’s begin!</p>

<p>Start by being standing. Stand for 10 breaths. Breath in and out as you wish. But, keep count.</p>

<p>Now, sit down on the ground (straw optional, and a pillow is nice if you have one for a cushion).</p>

<p>Take 5 deep breaths. In and out. Pause and focus your mind on your surroundings, eyes closed. What do you hear? Bird chirping? People talking? Just take mental note and be mindful about it. Now, another 5 breaths. Same way. Notice again. One more time, 5 breaths.</p>

<p>On the third try don’t try to notice anything and recite ‘om mani peme hum (hri)’ 108 times! Use the mala to count. And don’t verbalise the ‘hri’ part. Say it “inside your head” like you are reading it. Try to block out outside distractions while you do this.</p>

<p>Once this is done, use the Buddha stone and touch it to your mala. Eyes can be open. You’re done. Relax and recline for the rest of the time. Take in the sunshine! Breathe fresh air! Have some water!</p>

<p>When the timer is done, have some fresh matcha. Or drink when stone touches mala for 1min.</p>

<p>Total time: 15-60min. with stone, 45-180min. without stone, 90-360min. without mala and stone, 60sec. if you wear a special watch (quartz), special instructions (where it for the whole day, it releases energy like Buddha for the whole day, solar powered too, don’t eat anything while wearing it, drinks only. Water is good. Chocolate is good. Just these two for rest of day. Water and chocolate if you are hungry).</p>

<p>You can meditate for more than 15min, but the minimum is 15min. The more time you put in, the stronger the charge.</p>

<p>That’s it!</p>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/10/buddas/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Birthday Meditation</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/10/birthday/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>Try it out on your birthday!</p>

<p>Sound: Lambda Waves</p>

<p>Start with 10 deep breaths. Then 10 shallow ones. Then 6 deep breaths, conclude with 6 shallow ones.</p>

<p>End by holding for 3 seconds!</p>

<p>It makes the philosopher stone frequency higher! You’ll heal the brain faster.</p>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/10/birthday/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Accessing the 9th Chakra</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/10/9th-chakra/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>So, it is time to reach the 9th chakra? Let’s try it!</p>

<p>What you’ll need:</p>

<ol>
  <li>shungite water: let shungite soak in water for at least 15 minutes. Drink some prior to meditation.</li>
</ol>

<p>Now it is time to meditate! This meditation is for 15 minutes. You can have a helper stone like quartz or a moonstone. A cinntamani also wouldn’t be so bad either, too!</p>

<p>This one has the chakra association with the crown, don’t use third eye, it does n’t help you see yourself.</p>

<p>Start with 20 deep breaths, then do 10 shallow breaths right after the 20. Then hold for 30 seconds. From here, do 10 shallow breaths and then right after these 10 do 20 deep breaths again. Hold for 30 seconds. Now, this is the last part: do 20 deep breaths and 20 shallow breaths. Hold for 60 seconds. This should put you at the 9th.</p>

<p>To let this one grow, do the meditation 60 times! You’re gonna see some fun and not so fun stuff about yourself! Like seeing you from a different view.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>“Oh, I think I am like this, but I’m really like that.” Maybe you’ll think. Some stuff you won’t like about yourself and other stuff you’ll just love! You’ll see it all, your good, bad, pretty, ugly, dumb, cleaver, and so on….</p>
</blockquote>

<p>How you think you are isn’t how you really are. Same with others, how they see you isn’t how you really are.</p>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/10/9th-chakra/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Accessing the 12th Chakra</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/10/12th-chakra/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>You’ll need a helper stone to do this, choose from red carnelian, amethyst, or lemon quartz.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Wear something magnetic before meditation. Iron or neodymium is okay. This is for the brain and nerves! Make sure to follow up with philosopher stone water!!! Do this one alone. No one around. The 11-12 chakras are meant to be done alone, by yourself. No one can really be there to help you, but others can give you guidance. Chakras 1-10 you can be around people or have them in mind. The last 2 must be alone. Animals around you is fine for 1-12.  Be distant from others for the last 2, by a tree stump alone. Maybe 6 feet distance or something.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>This one is tricky, it’s the highest one for now.</p>

<p>Start by taking in 50 deep breaths! Then, hold the breath for 30 seconds, exhale, and do 40 deep breaths. Hold for 10 seconds and do another set of 10 breaths. Then, hold the breath for 30 seconds. Conclude with 12 shallow breaths.</p>

<p>Done!</p>

<p>To let this chakra manifest, do 30/30 meditations with 2 extra!</p>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/10/12th-chakra/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Accessing the 11th Chakra</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/10/11th-chakra/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>To reach the 11th chakra, follow these steps!</p>

<p>Since this is a higher chakra outside of the main 7, you’ll need a helper stone.</p>

<p>You’ll need a stone to assist you, use black obsidian and hold on to it during the meditation. Keep the meditation for 10min.</p>

<p>Start by taking in deep breaths, 20 inside and out. Each inhale and exhale is 1 count.</p>

<p>Then, hold the breath for 1 minute or 60 seconds. You’ll feel lightheaded and this is okay.</p>

<p>Exhale, and start again. Do this process a total of 3 times, 60 breaths total.</p>

<p>The meditation is done! End with one inhale and exhale.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>This meditation is best done at night.</p>
</blockquote>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/10/11th-chakra/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Accessing 10th Chakra</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/10/10th-chakra/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>Used for activating the ground chakra. It can heal:</p>

<ol>
  <li>memory problems</li>
  <li>looking out for yourself</li>
  <li>speaking more on your mind</li>
  <li>finding a hobby</li>
  <li>doing things you want more</li>
  <li>relaxing more</li>
  <li>loosening up stiff sores or muscles</li>
  <li>having a sense of security by yourself</li>
  <li>welcoming more views and accepting them</li>
  <li>sleeping better! insomnia gone.</li>
  <li>setting your bedtime juuuust right</li>
  <li>eating what need to eat better, food choices (plants taste like adrenochrome if you know how to spread the chakra in garden).</li>
</ol>

<blockquote>
  <p>Only do this meditation after you have some experience with the crown chakra. You can mix crown chakra water with adrenochrome water prior and drink it if you want to jump right in. This chakra is the 10th so the more you have meditated prior with the crown, the better you can reach it. If you just jump right in without preparation, it will be hard   to make progress. Adrenochrome tea or other things like it can save you some time from crown chakra meditation. You must drink prior though.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>You don’t need a mala with you, but carry a bloodstone for the session.</p>

<p>Time: 8-12min. More time means better activation. Go in multiples of 12 if you want more time, eg 36min.</p>

<p>Sub-chakra: crown! Don’t use third eye for this one.</p>

<p>Hold the bloodstone with your right hand and begin with shallow breathing.</p>

<p>In and out, in and out. Do this 36 times. You shouldn’t feel winded at all.</p>

<p>After that. Pause for a bit and begin deep breathing.</p>

<p>For deep breathing, take a deep breath in, hold it for 1 second, then release slowly. Do this 22 times.</p>

<p>Then, you can relax for the remainder of the time. The chakra is activating now and healing you. You’re going to feel drowsy and not like opening the eyes by now. That means it is working.</p>

<p>Follow this up with adrenochrome tea, all vegan and healthy. This will take the drowzy feeling away and you’ll have energy for the day.</p>

<p>You can also use another bloodstone, soak it in a glass bottle, and drink some ‘adrenochrome’ water as well in place of tea. You’ll need to make sure to have prepared the bloodstone so it mimics adrenochrome. It’s not adrenochrome, but something like it.</p>

<p>The adrenochrome type substance is a mild type of healing, used to rejuvenate the body for a little while. You’ll need it every now and then.</p>

<p>While you’re at the 10th chakra, you can charge a ground chakra stone! The stone is ruby. The metal is: platinum. Gold enhanced with a cinntamani also works. When in doubt, try a platinum bracelet!</p>

<p>But plain gold will not do.</p>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/10/10th-chakra/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
        
            <item>
                <title>Accessing the Divine Chakra</title>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/09/chakra-8/</link>
                <content:encoded>
                    <![CDATA[
                    <p>A meditation used to access the 8th chakra. Works best with a root chakra stone in your pocket. You want to commune with divine beings (gods), this is their chakra. Have some fun times!!!</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>For the 7 day access, eat some food prior, no meals! Usually this method takes 34/34 days. But, if you want to speed up the time, eat tons of food and bring quintessence. Drink it midway in meditation! Don’t worry about your health. After, drink philosopher stone water.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Sound: Lambda waves
Time: 10min.</p>

<p>What to have prior:</p>

<ol>
  <li>Orange Juice</li>
  <li>Sacral Chakra, Crown Chakra, and Jade stone water (minerals)</li>
  <li>bonus: philosopher stone water</li>
</ol>

<p>Dilute with tap water.</p>

<p>What to have after:</p>

<ol>
  <li>Orange Juice</li>
  <li>Crown Chakra, Sacral Chakra, and Jade stone water</li>
  <li>Ginger ale</li>
</ol>

<h3 id="how-to-meditate">How to Meditate</h3>

<p>Start by seating yourself on a mat. Be outside for this meditation, on rainy days don’t do it! It will be hard for you to access it then.</p>

<p>Begin with small breaths, do 27 small breaths. (Drink quintessence here.) In and out. Then, chant your favourite mantra 108 times with the mala to keep count. Then, do 52 big breaths! These have to be like innnnnnn and oooooouuuut.</p>

<p>You’re here now! Relax for the next 5 minutes or until the meditation is over. It’s a 10 minute meditation, so the remainder of the time try to just relax. Focus on sounds around you, the weather, and so on.</p>

<p>If you’d like, you can charge an 8th chakra stone while you meditate on selenite. The stone is: Sapphire.</p>

                    ]]>
                </content:encoded>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">/2022/11/09/chakra-8/</guid>
                <description>
                    
                </description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <author>Ramneek Narayan</author>
            </item>
        
    
  </channel>
</rss>
